你怎么跑到我手机里的
How'd you get in my phone?
这是不是意味着那天我们通话时
Does this mean when we talked the other day
你知道我是在厕所里
that you knew I was in the can?
我这下知道了
I do now.
会议展示做得怎么样
How was the presentation?
非常顺利
Actually went really well.
客户喜欢我们的新设计
The client loves the whole re-design.
但希望我们换掉长方形把手
They just want us to swap out the handles --
-该死的  -我懂的
- Damn it! - I know.
只有蠢货才会想要旋钮
Only knobs want knobs.
不是  是乔咬了我  他在出牙
No, Joe bit me. He's teething.
我觉得安迪这周末请假
I don't think it's a coincidence
不是巧合
that Andy took the weekend off.
这孩子跟海狸似的
Kid's like a beaver.
我都不敢穿短裤了
I'm afraid to wear short pants.
好啊  克莱尔
Hola, Claire.
好啊  歌洛莉亚
Hey, Gloria.
出差怎么样  玩得开心吗
How's your trip? Are you having any fun?
是啊  风有点大  但是
Uh...yeah. You know, it's a little windy, but, eh.